https://www.sjbmw.com/privacy/

Visit our showroom from home! New
We support social distancing and now provide virtual showroom visits. Select your preferred app to video conference with us or learn more.
Video conference with us or Learn more.
Fill out the form below to sign up for this deal.
Privacy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Pixel Motion and San Jose BMW Motorcycles. Pixel Motion and San Jose BMW Motorcycles promote the use of fair information practices. Because Pixel Motion and San Jose BMW Motorcycles are committed to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE:
Pixel Motion is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. Pixel Motion and San Jose BMW Motorcycles will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Pixel Motion and San Jose BMW Motorcycles collect information from our users at several different points on the web site.
VEHICLE QUOTE REQUESTS:
In order to obtain a vehicle price quote, a user must first complete a Quote Request Form. A user is required to give their contact information (such as name, address, telephone number and e-mail address). This information is used to contact the user and provide the quote or other information that they have requested. It is optional for the user to provide financial information, but can be done so that San Jose BMW Motorcycles can review and pre-qualify the user for financing if they are interested. All customer information obtained via the quote request form is encrypted for security purposes and stored on a secured server.
ORDERS:
Information is requested from the user on the e-Catalog order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If San Jose BMW Motorcycles has trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. All customer information obtained via the order form is encrypted for security purposes and stored on a secured server.
COOKIES:
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For example, a cookie is used to store items during e-Catalog shopping so that a list of what you are ordering is maintained. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use the site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user, may not be able to use the e-Catalog shopping basket function on the site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on the site.
LOG FILES:
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic and geographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
SHARING:
We may share demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is generally not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. However, Pixel Motion and/or San Jose BMW Motorcycles may send E-mails or mail about special offers at the Dealership or other offers or information that may be of interest to the user based on the information we collect. San Jose BMW Motorcycles uses an outside company (such as UPS, USPS, Fed Ex. etc.) to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not to our knowledge, retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
LINKS:
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Pixel Motion and San Jose BMW Motorcycles are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
SURVEY AND CONTESTS:
From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or may offer contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code and age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES:
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
SECURITY:
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.
When our quote request or order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just “surfing”.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, has restricted access at Pixel Motion and at the dealership. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, order clerk, sales representative, or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Access to the information is made via a password-protected site. Each time an employee needs to access information, they must enter their password to gain access to the information. Furthermore, employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Employees are periodically notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected.
SUPPLEMENTATION OF INFORMATION:
In order for this web site to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it may be necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources.
For example, to determine if customers qualify for financing, the dealership may use their name and social security number to request a credit report or approval from a lending institution.
SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES:
Pixel Motion and San Jose BMW Motorcycles may send the user site and service announcement updates which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regard to issues relating to their account via e-mail or phone.
CORRECTING / UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION:
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as address or E-mail), or if a user no longer desires to receive information from Pixel Motion and San Jose BMW Motorcycles, we will endeavor to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data from our database.
Contacting the Web Sites
If you have questions concerning this Privacy Policy or the practices of these sites, you may contact us.
Additional information regarding Pixel Motion Privacy Policy can be found here.
All New InventoryUsed InventoryFinancingSchedule ServiceSan Jose BMW Motorcycles
1990 W San Carlos St, San Jose, CA 95128Get Directions
Call us today!
408-618-2154
SalesSales Department HoursMonday: CLOSED - GONE RIDINGTuesday: 9:00AM - 5:00PMWednesday: 9:00AM - 5:00PMThursday: 9:00AM - 5:00PMFriday: 9:00AM - 5:00PMSaturday: 9:00AM - 5:00PMSunday: CLOSED - GONE RIDING
©2020. San Jose BMW Motorcycles. All Rights Reserved.
Directions
Privacy
Terms
Contact Us
Careers
Sitemap
Click to call sales
While great effort is made to ensure the accuracy of the information on this site, errors can occur.
Please verify all pricing information with a customer service representative.
This is easily done by calling us or visiting us at the dealership.
My Vehicles
Listed below are your saved and recently viewed vehicles
CLOSE X
My Saved Vehicles ()
My Recently Viewed Vehicles ()
Compare
Vehicles
|
Logout
You can also view your saved vehicles on other devices.
Sign up
Sign In
Save your vehicles.
Have your vehicles with you
Save your favorite vehicles for later viewing on your desktop or mobile devices.
Recently Viewed Vehicles
Keep track of all the vehicles you've viewed for a better car shopping experience.
Compare saved vehicles
Narrow your search by comparing your favorite vehicles.
Log in to view your saved vehicles.
Enter your email
Sign Up
Sign In
Already registered? Sign in.
Or sign up to access your saved vehicles and
recently viewed vehicles on all your devices.
Vehicle Comparison
CLOSE
Condition
Price
Year
Make
Model
Trim
Select total out of pocket
$0 out of pocket$1 to $500 out of pocket$501 to $1,000 out of pocket$1,001 to $1,500 out of pocket$1,501 to $2,000 out of pocket$2,001 to $2,500 out of pocket$2,501 to $3,000 out of pocketOver $3,001 out of pocket
Select Your Mileage
10,000 mi. / yr
12,000 mi. / yr
15,000 mi. / yr
First Name
Last Name
Phone
Message
Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Get a Quick Quote
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip Code*Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Start My Purchase
×
Schedule Service
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeDate
Date Format: MM slash DD slash YYYY
Date entered above will be confirmed by a service advisor.What service do you need?
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Order Parts
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeWhat parts are you looking for?
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Value Your Trade
What vehicle are you interested in?
Filling out this section helps us evaluate the purchase of the new/used bike, and trade-in potential values of your current bike.
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeWhat vehicle are you trading in?
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Make an Offer
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMessage
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Check Availability
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMessage
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Special Offers
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMessage
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Commercial Request
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip Code
New (709)
Ram (262)
Model
Ram 1500
Ram 2500
Ram 3500
Ram ProMaster 2500
Ram ProMaster 3500
Ram ProMaster 1500
Ram ProMaster City
Year
2016
2017
Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Contact Us
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip Code*Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
Models BMW
Piaggio
Vespa
Zero
AdventureHeritageRoadsterSportTourUrban Mobility20212021 K 1600 Grand America2019C 400 X2020C 650 GT2019C 650 GT2018C Evolution2021F 750 GS2021F 750 GS2020F 750 GS2021F 850 GS2021F 850 GS2020F 850 GS2021 F 850 GS Adventure2020F 850 GS Adventure2021F 850 GS Adventure2020F 900 R2021F 900 R2020F 900 XR2021F 900 XR2019G 310 GS2020G 310 GS2020G 310 R2019G 310 R2020K 1600 B2021K 1600 B2019K 1600 B2019K 1600 Grand America2020K 1600 Grand America2019K 1600 GT2020K 1600 GT2020K 1600 GTL2021K 1600 GTL2019K 1600 GTL2021M 1000 RR2021R 1250 GS2021R 1250 GS2021R 1250 GS2020R 1250 GS2019R 1250 GS2020R 1250 GS Adventure2021R 1250 GS Adventure2020R 1250 R2021R 1250 RS2020R 1250 RS2020R 1250 RT2021R 182021R 18 Classic2020R nineT2019R nineT2020R nineT /52020R nineT Pure2020R nineT Scrambler2020S 1000 R2021S 1000 R2020S 1000 RR2021S 1000 XR2020S 1000 XR2021S1000 RRBVFlyLibertyMP3TyphoonWi-Bike2019BV 3502019Fly 1502019 Fly 502019Liberty 1502019Liberty 502019Liberty S 1502019Liberty S 50 Euro 42019MP3 SPORT 5002019Typhoon 1252019Typhoon 502019Wi-Bike Active2019 Wi-Bike Comfort946ElettricaGTSGTS SuperPrimaveraSei GiorniSprint2019(946) RED2019ELETTRICA 4 KW2019GTS 300 HPE2019GTS SUPER 300 HPE2019GTS SUPER 300 NOTTE 3002019PRIMAVERA 150 50° ANNIVERSARIO2019PRIMAVERA 150 CC2019PRIMAVERA 150 SPORT2019PRIMAVERA 150 TOURING MY192019PRIMAVERA 150 TOURING MY202019PRIMAVERA 150 YACHT CLUB2019PRIMAVERA 50 50° ANNIVERSARIO2019PRIMAVERA 50 CC2019PRIMAVERA 50 TOURING2019PRIMAVERA 50 YACHT CLUB2019SEI GIORNI 300 HPE2019SPRINT 150 CC2019SPRINT 150 NOTTE2019SPRINT 150 SPORT2019SPRINT 50 CC2019SPRINT 50 NOTTE2019SPRINT 50 SPRINT S2019DS2019DSR2019FX2019FXS2020S2020SR2020SR F2020SR S
